USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  - Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1941
    - Part of U.S. Fleet Taken from Crow's Nest of USS Arizona, 1936, 84-37-75 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Ferry, Seattle to Bremerton, WA, 84-37-76, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Pineapples, Hawaii, 84-37-77, circa 1936 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Denver Jenkins, Wrestler, Wearing All Navy Belt, 1927-1928, 63-5-1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Navy Propaganda Photographs of Two Japanese Two Person Submarines, 67-7-1, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - USS West Virginia Engulfed in Flames During Pearl Harbor Attack, December 7, 1941, 67-1-2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Engulfed in Smoke, December 7, 1941, 67-1-3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Official U.S. Navy Photograph, Shaw Engulfed in Smoke, December 7, 1941, 67-1-4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Official U.S. Navy Photograph Magazine of the Shaw Explodes, 67-1-5, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - United Stated Navy Photograph Stricken Battleships. Left to Right: USS West Virginia Severely Damaged, USS Tennessee Damaged, USS Arizona, December 7, 1941, 67-1-6 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - United States Navy Photograph Rescue Workers Burned Holes in Capsized USS Oklahoma to Rescue Men Trapped Below USS. Marlyland, Negative Included, December 7, 1941, 67-1-7 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Rescue with Recovery Mission, December 7, 1941, 67-1-8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - United States Navy Photograph Sailors Man Boats at Side of Burning USS West Virginia Disregarding Danger of Explosions. Note National Colors Flying, December 7, 1941, 67-1-9 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - United States Navy Photograph Smoke Pouring from USS Shaw, Bombed in Drydock (Right Center). Capsized USS Oglala in Front USS Helena, December 7, 1941, 67-1-10 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - United States Navy Photograph USS Maryland was Damaged Slightly and Was One of the First Ships to Rejoin Fleet. USS Oklahoma at Right, December 7, 1941, 67-1-11 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - United States Navy Photograph USS Nevada, After Being Hit By Bombs, is Beached at Hospital Point, December 7, 1941, 67-1-12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - United States Navy Photograph, Damage to USS West Virginia After Attack on Pearl Harbor, 67-1-13, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - United States Navy Photograph, Damage to USS Oklahoma After Attack on Pearl Harbor, 67-1-14, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - United States Navy Photograph Naval Air Station. This is the Wreckage Strewn Grounds at the Japanese Sneak Attack. An Explosion Had Just Occurred, 67-1-15, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - United States Navy Photograph Wrecked U.S. Navy Seaplane. One of the 80 Planes Wrecked by Japanese Bombs. This is an Observation Scout,, 67-1-16, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - United States Navy Photograph, Damage to Casson-Downs-Pennsylvania after Attack on Pearl Harbor, 67-1-17, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - United States Navy Photograph, USS Arizona Engulfed in Smoke, 67-1-18, 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Photograph of Japanese Propaganda Leaflet Found in Japanese Planes, 67-1-19, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Downed Japanese Plane, 67-1-20, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Photograph of Map Detailing Japanese Attack on Pearl Harbor, 67-1-21, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - USS Arizona Whale Boat Crew, 68-3-1, circa 1935 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - USS Arizona Whale Boat Crew, Fleet Champions 1922, 75-1-1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Arizona Crew, San Pedro, CA, 76-6-1, 1924 June (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Sailor Ralph Duncan Byard, 1932, 81-1-1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Sailor Ralph Duncan Byard, 1932, 81-1-2 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - USS Arizona Galley on the Dock, Bremerton, WA, circa 1939, 81-1-3 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Sailors Hoppy Hall and Mamma Basden Forde, 81-1-7, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Sailors Hoppy Hall and and Unidentified Sailor, 81-1-5, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Sailors Stanley and Mamma Basden Forde Docked in Bremerton, WA, circa 1939, 81-1-6 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Sailors Hoppy Hall, 81-1-7, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Baker, 3rd Class, 81-1-8, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, 81-1-9, circa 1938 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Commander R.D. Byard, Retired, 81-1-10, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Sailor Ed Kelpin on Dry Dock, 71-1-2, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Sailor Ed Kelpin with USS Arizona Dingy, 71-1-3, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ed Kelpin with Unidentified Sailor on Deck, 71-1-4, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ed Kelpin with Unidentified Woman, 71-1-5, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ed Kelpin with Unidentified Woman, 71-1-6, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sailor J.E. Kelpin on Dock, 71-1-7, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Ed Kelpin and Unidentified Sailor with Weapon Heads, 71-1-8, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Sailors Ed Kelpin and Jack Baker, 71-1-9, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Ed Kelpin and Unidentified Sailor Posing in Cutout on Long Beach, CA Boardwalk, 71-1-10, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Sailor Mickey on Deck, 71-1-11, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Bill, 71-1-12, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ed Kelpin on Deck, 71-1-13, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Sailor Getting Into Uniform on Deck, 71-1-14, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Jimmy Payne Working on Deck, 71-1-15, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Jimmy Payne Smoking a Pipe on Deck, 71-1-16, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Jimmy Payne Sitting on the Anchor Line, 71-1-17, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Jimmy Payne Posing on Deck, 71-1-18, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - M.C. Lawrence in Hawaii, 71-1-19, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - M.C. Lawrence at Hawaiian Village, Honolulu, HI, 71-1-20, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - M.C. Lawrence on Beach in Hawaii, 71-1-21, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Joe Garnett, Electrician, on Beach In Hawaii, 71-1-22, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Joe Garnet with King Kamehameha Statue, Honolulu, HI, 71-1-23, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Jack Baker with Pipe on Deck, 71-1-24, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Jack Baker with Pipe Sitting on a Boat on Deck, 71-1-25, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Jack Baker Sitting on Anchor Line, 71-1-26, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Jack Baker Posing on Deck, 71-1-27, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Jack Baker with Unidentified Woman, 71-1-28, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Sailors with Women on Dock, 71-1-29, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified Sailor and Unidentified Woman, 71-1-30, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Cash and Eva in Front of House, 71-1-31, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Ruth on Deck, 71-1-32, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Jane Randal in Sailor Outfit In Front of House, 71-1-3, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Levona Sharf in Costume, 71-1-34, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Eva, San Diego, CA, 71-1-35, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Eva and Margaret in Swimsuits on Front Porch, 71-1-36, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Mary on Front Porch, 71-1-37, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - USS Arizona Captain W. I. Tarrent U.S.N. and Commander A.L. Bristol Jr., U.S.N., 71-1-38, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Rowing Race, 71-1-39, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - USS Arizona Whale Boat Crew, 71-1-40, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Winning Race Boat Crew, 71-1-41, circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Ten Sailors on Beach, 71-1-42, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Row Boat Crew, 71-1-43, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Wrestling Team, 71-1-44, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Beach, Long Beach, CA, 71-1-45, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Saturday Morning Library Boating at Long Beach, CA, 71-1-46, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Navy Landing, Long Beach, CA, 71-1-47, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Anchored at Long Beach, CA, 71-1-48, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - A Seal on the Long Beach Life Buoy, 71-1-49, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona beneath the San Francisco, CA Bay Bridge, 71-1-50, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Alcatraz The Rock San Francisco Bay, CA, 71-1-51, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Alcatraz Prison, 71-1-52, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona Dry Dock, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-53, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona Dry Dock, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-54, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona Dry Dock, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-55, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Dry Dock, 71-1-56, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-57, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-58, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Dry Dock, Hunter Point, San Francisco, CA, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-59, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-60, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, View from Stern, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-61, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-62, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-63, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-64, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-65, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-66, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - USS Arizona in Bremerton Navy Yard, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-67, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - USS Arizona in Bremerton Navy Yard, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-68, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - The Staff Yacht in Bremerton Navy Yard, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-69, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-70, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona, Bremerton Liberty, Bremerton, WA, 71-1-71, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - USS Arizona at Anchor in Seattle, WA, 71-1-72, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Ship Outlined with Light Bulbs, Seattle, WA, 71-1-73, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Chinese-American Woman at the Army and Navy YMCA in Honolulu, HI, 71-1-74, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Bandstand at the Royal Palace in Honolulu, HI, 71-1-75, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Coral House, Oahu, HI, 71-1-76, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Coral House, Oahu, HI, 71-1-77, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Six Sailors Looking on the Oahu Valley from Pali, Oahu, HI, 71-1-78, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Diamond Head, Honolulu, HI, Photograph by Ed Kelpin, 71-1-79, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Lahaina Roads at Maui, HI, 71-1-80, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Pearl Harbor, HI, 71-1-81, circa 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - USS Arizona Entering Pearl Harbor, 71-1-82, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hawaii as Seen from Pearl Harbor, 71-1-83, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sailors Walking on a Volcano, 71-1-84, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 71-1-85, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Sea with Land in Background, 71-1-86, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Aircraft Carrier Lexington, 71-1-87, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Aboard a Cruiser, 71-1-88, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - A Destroyer Patrol Boat, 71-1-89, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - S.S. Bennekom, 71-1-90, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - USS Oklahoma Guns, 71-1-91, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Other Ships as Seen From Our Mainmast, 71-1-92, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Submarine, 71-1-93, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - USS Saratoga, 71-1-94, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Dewey's War Dog USS Olympia, 71-1-95, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Lowering a 14" Shell, 71-1-96, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Lowering a 14" Shell, 71-1-96, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - USS Texas, 71-1-98, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - USS Milwaukee, 71-1-99, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 3" Anti- Aircraft on Land, 71-1-100, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - USS Oklahoma Conning Tower, 71-1-101, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - USS Arizona Bow, 71-1-102, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Battle Fleet in Line Formation, 71-1-103, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Manchurce, 71-1-104, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Plane, 71-1-105, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Sailors on Deck, 71-1-106, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Wheels Carrying 3 Pieces, 71-1-107, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Wheels Carried Guns on Beach, 71-1-108, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - View on Deck, 71-1-109, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Gun, 71-1-110, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Ed Kelpin and Unidentified Sailor, 71-1-11, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Sailors on Deck, 71-1-112, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - View from Starboard, 71-1-113, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona Liberty Party, 71-1-114, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona Yard Party, 71-1-115, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Field Day, 71-1-116, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Sailors Fishing Off Deck, 71-1-117, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - The C In C Come Aboard, 71-1-118, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - The C in C Leaves, 71-1-119, circa 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - USS Arizona Aleutian Storm, 71-1-120, 1938 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - USS Arizona Aleutian Storm, 71-1-121, 1938 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - USS Arizona Aleutian Storm, 71-1-122, 1938 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - (Destroyer) 4 Stacker Approaches the Arizona for Refuel, 71-1-123, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Arizona Refueling a Can While Underway, 71-1-124, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Refueling a Can, 71-1-125, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Speed Run, 71-1-126, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Bow Spray, 71-1-127, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Underway, 71-1-128, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Evening off the Bow, 71-1-129, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Battle Row, 71-1-130, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Photograph Taken from Flight Bridge, 71-1-131, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - A Barge Approaches, 71-1-132, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Power Barge, 71-1-133, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Base Force Battle Fleet Formation, 71-1-134, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona Underway Speed Run, 71-1-135, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - A Brief Lull in the Storm, 71-1-136, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bow Rolling in the Trough, 71-1-137, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - White Caps hitting Bow, 71-1-138, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Bow of USS Arizona Hit by Waves, 71-1-139, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Four Unidentified Sailors in USS Arizona Motor Boat, 71-1-140, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - USS Arizona Long Range Gunnery, 71-1-141, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - USS Arizona Dock Side, 71-1-142, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - USS Arizona Search Light Display, 71-1-143, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - USS Arizona Plane Crack Up (Crash), 71-1-144, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - USS Arizona Planes, 71-1-145, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - USS Arizona Catapult, 71-1-146, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - USS Arizona After Plane, 71-1-147, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Planes on Deck of USS Arizona, 71-1-148, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Planes on Deck of USS Arizona, 71-1-149, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - A Plane Leaves the Catapult, 71-1-150, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Approaching Plane to be Picked Up, 71-1-151, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona at Anchor, 71-1-152, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - USS Arizona Air Bedding Clean Sweep Down Fore & Aft, 71-1-153, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Painting the Foremast, 71-1-154, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona Painting Foremast Detail, 71-1-155, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Sailors Working on Deck of USS Arizona, 71-1-156, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - USS Arizona Quarter Deck, 71-1-157, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - USS Arizona Quarter Deck, 71-1-158, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Engines, 71-1-159, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Electrical Pumps, 71-1-160, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Generator Rooms, 71-1-161, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Gauges in Engine Room, 71-1-162, circa 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - The Bridge, 71-1-163, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Forescastle, 71-1-164, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Forecastle Liberty, 71-1-165, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Forecastle Liberty at Sea, 71-1-166, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Forecastle Anchor Chain, 71-1-167, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Stern of USS Arizona, 71-1-168, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Scrub Hammocks, 71-1-169, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Big Pavarames, 71-1-170, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Decks Cleaned for Action, 71-1-171, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona Gun Deck, 71-1-172, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - no.1 Turret Trains Aft, 71-1-173, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona Mast, 71-1-174, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 71-1-175, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Sailor standing by for Colors, 71-1-176, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Sailors Running Gun Firing Drills on Deck of USS Arizona, 71-1-177, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - A 1-16 Gun Salute in Action, 71-1-178, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - USS Arizona no.1 Turret, 71-1-179, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - USS Arizona Bit Cleat, 71-1-180, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - View of Land Mass from Porthole, 71-1-181, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Motor Launches, 71-1-182, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - The Only Flag Flying Higher than the U.S. Flag, Christian Services Being Held,71-1-183, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Stairway on USS Arizona, 71-1-184, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - USS Arizona 36" Searchlight, 71-1-185, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - A Blast from the Whistle, 71-1-186, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - At Em', USS Arizona Mascot, 71-1-187, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sailors Swimming Off the USS Arizona, 71-1-188, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Swimming Party Possibly at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 71-1-189, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Sailor Posing with Anti-Aircraft Gun, 71-1-190, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Anti-Aircraft Gun, 71-1-191, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona 5" Gun at Night, 71-1-192, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified Ship, 71-1-193, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Ship, 71-1-194, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-195, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-196, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-197, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-198, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-199, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, Crossing the Equator, 71-1-200, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, Crossing the Line, 71-1-201, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-202, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-203, circa 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, 71-1-204, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Neptune's Court Ceremony, Initiation Tank, 71-1-205, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Panama Canal Locks, 71-1-206, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Panama Canal Locks, 71-1-207, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Dredge in Panama Canal, 71-1-208, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Two People at Gatun Dam, Panama Canal, 71-1-209, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Panama Canal, 71-1-210, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Panama Canal, 71-1-211, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Passing Through the Panama Canal Locks, 71-1-212, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal Locks, 71-1-213, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 71-1-214, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal Locks, 71-1-215, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 71-1-216, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 71-1-217, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal with Sailors on Deck, 71-1-218, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - USS Arizona Tropical Awning in Panama Canal, 71-1-219, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - USS Arizona in the South Pacific, 71-1-220, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - USS Arizona at Dock in Panama, 71-1-221, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - View of Panama Canal Landscape from USS Arizona, 71-1-222, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Ships in Panama Canal, 71-1-223, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - View of Panama Canal Landscape, 71-1-224, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - USS Arizona Docked in Panama Canal, 71-1-225, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Sailor Standing in front of Drink Sign on Panama Street, 71-1-226, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sailors Standing in Front of Building in Panama, 71-1-227, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - USS Arizona in the Panama Canal, 71-1-228, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - USS Arizona Motor Boats and Launches at Panama Canal, 71-1-229, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Sailors on USS Arizona Deck in Panama Canal, 71-1-230, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Waterfall in Panama Canal, 71-1-231, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Photograph of Waterfall Taken from USS Arizona Deck, 71-1-232, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Sailor Looking at Waterfall in Panama Canal, 71-1-233, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Child Standing in front of Building in Panama, 71-1-234, circa 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 31)